dopdf.com 2018-12-14

# Privacy Policy

Effective date: May 22, 2018

Softland SRL ("us", "we", or "our") operates the http://www.doPDF.com/ website (the "Website") and doPDF application (the "App").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the website/app. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

##  Specific notices regarding the software available on this website

The materials on Softland SRL’s ("Softland") World Wide Web Servers ("Site") are provided as a service to its customers and may be used for informational purposes only. Copies may be downloaded subject to the provisions below. By downloading any materials from this site, you agree to these terms. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use the site or download any materials from it. Nothing contained herein shall be construed as conferring any license or right under any Softland copyright.

DOCUMENTS PUBLISHED BY SOFTLAND ON THEIR SITES ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" BASIS, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. SOFTLAND SHALL NOT UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES BE LIABLE TO ANY PERSON FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES RESULTING FROM USE OF OR RELIANCE ON THE INFORMATION PRESENTED, LOSS OF PROFIT, REVENUES OR COSTS OF REPLACEMENT GOODS, EVEN IF INFORMED IN ADVANCE OF THE POSSIBILITY OF DAMAGES.

Every effort has been made to ensure the accuracy of the information presented. However, Softland assumes no responsibility for the accuracy of the information. The information presented on the site is subject to change without notice. Softland may make improvements and/or changes in the products and/or the programs described on the site at any time without notice. Mention of third party products or services is for information purposes only and constitutes neither an endorsement nor a recommendation.

##  Collection, processing and passing of personal data

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Website and App for you.

####  Data Collected by Softland

While using our Website, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Below is a detailed list of the information we collect and how we use it.

**Contacting us**

When you contact us using the contact form via the Website or emailing us directly, any personally identifiable information you send to us is only used to identify you as a client and help with your support issue. We use Google Apps to manage email correspondence. We also archive all the emails. We do not share your email correspondence details with other third party providers. We do not use your email address collected via the online form to send you promotional emails.

When you contact us via the telephone, any personally identifiable information you send to us is only used to identify you as a client and help with your support issue. No information is recorded or archived. We do not share your phone number with other third party providers. We do not use your phone number to contact you with promotions.

**Using the Forum**

We have a user forum powered by phpBB (an open source forum software). When you register to become a member of the forum or login and start posting we collect the information you submit to us to allow you access to the forum: a uniquely identifiable user name, your personal password and email address. Any other information is optional and you can decide what information will be displayed publicly. We do not use your email address collected via the forum to send you promotional emails.

**Newsletter**

When you subscribe to our mailing list you provide us a valid email address. This is stored on our hosting company's servers. We use your email address to notify you occasionally of newly released versions or other updates. You can unsubscribe at any time from our mailing database to stop receiving these notifications.

**App usage statistics**

In order to help development and improve our App's features, the installer has a setting for collection of usage data. This function collects anonymous App usage data and sends it to Google Analytics. The data is used in development to get reliable statistics on which features are used (or not used). This data is anonymous and does not personally identify you. You can opt out of sending anonymous usage statistics during the setup or later from the App options.

During the installation process, anonymous statistics are sent and stored on Softland's servers. These stats help us discover setup errors and improve the installation user experience. This data is anonymous and does not personally identify you.

For bug tracking purposes, you can send us crash/exception logs that help us improve the app. These logs have an optional setting to include your email address, which we only use to get back to you when we fix the bug.

**Tracking & Cookies**

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Website and App and hold certain information. Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Website and App. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Website.

####  Data Collected by Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate access to our Products and Services ("Service Providers"), to provide various services on our behalf or to assist us in analyzing how our Products and Services are used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these services on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**Facebook Comments and social buttons (Facebook)**  
Facebook Comments/Social button is a service provided by Facebook Inc. that allows users to share comments/like some pages of our Website and share them on the Facebook Platform. Place of Data Processing for the collected data is USA. For details regarding Facebook's policy on data processing via Facebook comments/social button see [ www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation.php)

**Google +1 Button (Google)**  
Google +1 is a service managed by Google Inc., which allows users to publicly share information and to receive personalized content from Google and its partners. The information the user provides to Google through our Website is used according to Google Privacy Policy. Place of Data Processing for the collected data is USA. For details regarding Google's policy on data processing via Google +1 Buttons see [www.google.com/intl/en/+/policy/+1button.html](http://www.google.com/intl/en/+/policy/+1button.html)

**Twitter social buttons (Twitter)**  
This is a service supplied by Twitter that allows users to push a button on our Website ("Twitter Button") and share liking of our Website on Twitter.com without having to exit the page. Place of Data Processing for the collected data is USA. For details regarding Twitter's policy on data processing via the Twitter Button see [twitter.com/privacy](https://twitter.com/privacy).

**Google Adsense (Google)**  
The advertising services provided by third parties may allow the Website to use user’s data for commercial communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on the Website based on Users’ interests.

Google Adsense is an advertising platform that indexes all or part of the data of the Website. Google may also record through "DoubleClick" cookies the visiting user's behavior while interacting with the Website. These cookies are used by Google and third parties to show different advertisements on the basis of user’s previous behavior. The Users may decide to disable all the DoubleClick cookies by visiting this optout URL: [www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/optout?hl=en)

The place of Data Processing for the collected data is USA. For details regarding Google's policy on data processing via Google Adsense see: [google.com/privacy/ads/](https://google.com/privacy/ads/)

**Google Analytics (Google)**  
Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"), which uses "cookies" to collect Users’ Personal Data which are forwarded to, and deposited on, Google's servers in the United States. Google uses the Data collected to track and examine the Website’s usage, prepare reports on the Website’s activities for the website managers and supply other optional services. Google may use the collected Data to carry out behavioral targeting of the Website’s Users. Google does not associate the user's IP address with any other information in Google's possession. Any refusal to utilize the cookies, by selecting the appropriate setup on your browser, may prevent the use of some functions of this Website. The place of Data Processing for the collected data is USA. For details regarding Google's policy on data processing via Google Analytics see: [www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

**Other ad networks (Google)**  
We may use advertising services provided by third parties via Revive, an ad management solution. These 3rd party advertising networks use User’s Data for commercial communication purposes displayed in the form of banners and other advertisements on the Website based on Users’ interests.

**Amazon SES (Amazon)**  
Softland uses an email management service, provided by Amazon, to allow us to manage and monitor lists of the email addresses of our Website and App users and communicate with them via email.

Amazon SES is a mailing list provider created and operated by Amazon Inc. It makes possible to manage databases of contacts for sending emails. The service allows collecting information relating to the date and time when emails were opened by the User and the numbers of clicks by the User. The Place of Data Processing for collected information is USA. For details regarding Amazon's policy on data processing via Amazon SES see: [https://aws.amazon.com/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html)

**ReliableSite**

This is our hosting provider and we use their servers to make our Website available to you. Place of Data Processing for the collected data is USA. For details regarding ReliableSite's policy on data processing via their servers see <https://www.reliablesite.net/policies/privacy.aspx>

##  Use of Your Personal Information

Softland uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain the Website and App
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or App
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Website when you choose to do so
  * To provide customer care and support
  * To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Website or App
  * To monitor the usage of the Website and App
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To make the Website or related services easier to use by eliminating the need to re-enter the same information (login)
  * To send certain mandatory service communications such as information on technical service issues, security announcements.

##  Transfer Of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

Personal information collected by Softland through its sites, apps and services may also be stored and processed by third-party partners to be able to provide you our products/services (i.e. payment processors). By using our web site or a Softland product/service you agree that your personal information may be transferred to any country in which Softland or its affiliates, subsidiaries or distribution partners maintain facilities.

Softland will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

##  Removal procedures

As all information is collected via opt-in methods, we believe all information you receive from Softland will be relevant to your computing needs. However, if you do not wish to receive communications from us or want your details removed from our server you can contact us at office@softlandro.com.

##  Disclosure Of Data

Softland may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Softland
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Website or App
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Website or App to the public
  * To protect against legal liability

##  Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

##  Links To Other Sites

Our Website and App may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

##  Children's Privacy

Our Website and App do not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children"). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

##  Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

##  Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

  * By email: office@softlandro.com

##  Trademarks

All product and brand names mentioned in this Site are trademarks or registered trademarks of their respective holders.

## License Agreement (EULA)

The software made available to you by Softland has its own End-User License Agreement (EULA) that you have to agree to during the installation in order to be able to start using it. You are advised to read it before finishing the installation. If you want to print and/or read those before starting the installation, you can download it here:  
Download doPDF EULA (PDF)
